<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Explore Switzerland</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search">Search destination</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Symbols of Switzerland</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab">TabActivity</string>
    <string name="hint_search"><i>Search destination</i></string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab_proba">TabProbaActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_symbols_of_switzerland">Symbols of Switzerland</string>
    <string name="tab_about_switzerland">About Switzerland</string>
    <string name="tab_explore_cantons_a">Explore</string>
    <string name="tab_explore_cantons_b">cantons</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab_layout">Tab Layout Activity</string>
    <string name="title_my_tab_factory">My tab factory</string>
    <string name="title_explore_fragment">Explore Fragment</string>
    <string name="title_about_fragment">About fragment</string>
    <string name="title_symbols_fragment">Symbols fragment</string>
    <string name="title_my_sample_fragment">My sample fragment</string>
    <string name="title_my_page_adapter">My page adapter</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cantons_luzern">CantonsLuzern</string>
    <string name="about_text_bg"><b>Switzerland</b> (German: Schweiz, French: Suisse, Italian: Svizzera, Romansch: Svizra, Latin: Confoederatio Helvetica) is a landlocked country in Central Europe. It has borders with France to the west, Italy to the south, Austria and Liechtenstein to the east and Germany to the north.</string>
    <string name="about_climate_title">CLIMATE</string>
    <string name="about_text_climate">The climate is temperate, but varies with altitude. Switzerland has cold, cloudy, rainy/snowy winters and cool to warm, cloudy, humid summers with occasional showers.</string>
    <string name="about_politics_title">POLITICS</string>
    <string name="about_text_politics">Switzerland\'s independence and neutrality have long been honored by the major European powers and Switzerland was not involved in either of the two World Wars. The political and economic integration of Europe over the past half century, as well as Switzerland\'s role in many UN and international organizations has strengthened Switzerland\'s ties with its neighbors. However, the country did not officially become a UN member until 2002. Switzerland remains active in many UN and international organizations, but retains a strong commitment to neutrality.</string>
    <string name="about_culture_title">CULTURE</string>
    <string name="about_text_culture">Switzerland showcases three of Europe\'s most distinct cultures. To the northeast is the clean and correct, 8-to-5-working, stiffer Swiss-German-speaking Switzerland; to the southwest you find the wine drinking and laissez-faire style known from the French; in the southeast, south of Alps, the sun warms cappuccino-sippers loitering in Italian-style piazzas; and in the center: classic Swiss alphorns and mountain landscapes. Binding it all together is a distinct Swiss mentality.</string>
    <string name="about_economy_title">ECONOMY</string>
    <string name="about_text_economy"></string>
    <string name="about_dialects_title">DIALECTS &#38; CITIES</string>
    <string name="about_text_dialects_a">Remark: All Swiss cities, villages, regions, 
or whatever geographical object do have 
official spellings in all four national 
languages; sometimes they are just the 
same. However, major cities and touristic 
regions also know official English spellings. 
Nevertheless, only a few years ago, the 
official Swiss tourism office started to 
advertise major spots and cities with their 
original, local spelling; with some 
exceptions of course, such as Geneva and 
Zurich for example. Obviously, it was too 
disturbing for anglo-saxon tourists to 
remember all the different spellings. But 
their real spellings are really important to 
the locals and helpful to know as a tourist 
of the respective region. So therefore, the 
following list will present you the 
advertised spelling first, followed with its 
local spelling, if different, then its English 
version, if different, and its other national 
spellings.
You could even enlarge this lists with other 
different, but hardly anymore used or even 
outdated spellings in other national 
languages (e.g. Bellinzona used to be 
spelled Bellenz in German or Bellence in
 French, or even more oudated: Lugano 
was known as Lauis in German). And this 
can even get escalated if you would want to 
refer to the different spellings of the 
different dialects in the different national 
language regions of Switzerland: the many 
21+ Swiss-German dialects, the four 
Romansh dialects, the Franco-Provençal 
from the French speaking Switzerland, or 
the Lombard in Ticino.
And how to speak them is even another 
issue, since even if they are written the 
same, they are quite often not spoken the 
same way in the different 
languages/dialects, of course.</string>
    <string name="about_text_dialects_basel">Basel (ger ; eng: Basle (somehow outdated, however still used in the English press); fre: Bâle; ita/roh: Basilea) — the traveller\'s gateway to the German Rhineland and French Alsace with an exceptional medieval downtown at the knee of the Rhine river; excellent museums (~40) and art\'s mecca during ART BASEL, world\'s largest art fair; also famous for its huge and contemplating carnival around February (Basler Fasnacht); German-speaking world wide renowned theatre (including opera and ballet).</string>
    <string name="about_text_dialects_bellinzona">Bellinzona (ita/eng/ger/roh ; fre: 
Bellinzone) — renowned for its medieval 
castles, world UNESCO heritage, pretty 
center and capital of the canton of Ticino, 
overlooking one of the few flat rural areas 
of Switzerland towards Lake Maggiore.</string>
    <string name="about_text_dialects_chur">Chur (ger ; roh: Cuira; eng/fre: Coire; ita: 
Coira) — capital of the canton of Grisons 
(ger: Kanton Graubünden; roh: Chantun 
Grischun; ita: Cantone dei Grigioni), the 
only trilingual Swiss canton, in the 
east-south of Switzerland, dates back 
almost 4000 years; lovely old town; gate to 
several glitzy ski and hiking resorts, such 
as St. Moritz, Davos, Arosa, Lenzerheide, 
Flims/Laax and many more; major hub to 
the Glacier Express and the Bernina Express.</string>
    <string name="about_text_dialects_bern">Bern (ger ; eng/fre: Berne; ita/roh: Berna) — 
capital of Switzerland at the shores of the 
cristal-clear green-blue Aare river with an 
amazingly well preserved old-town with 
arcades along almost every street; great 
restaurants abound, as do bars and clubs.</string>
    <string name="about_text_dialects_geneva">Geneva (eng ; fre: Genève; ger: Genf; ita: 
Ginevra; roh: Genevra) — this centre of arts 
and culture is an international city that is 
home to around 200 governmental and 
non-governmental organizations (with 
some major UN organizations) at the end o
f Lake Geneva (Lac Léman flows into the 
river Rhône), founding place of Calvinism 
and THE Red Cross (ICRC); almost every 
second inhabitant is a foreigner.</string>
    <string name="about_text_dialects_interlaken">Interlaken (ger/eng/fre/ita/roh) — the 
outdoor and action sports capital of 
Switzerland; anything from skydiving, 
bungee jumping, hiking, white-water 
rafting, to canyoning; between the two lakes 
Brienz and Thun; starting point for many, 
many tourists for excursions into the 
Bernese Alps.</string>
    <string name="about_text_dialects_lausanne">Lausanne (fre/eng/ger ; ita/roh: Losanna) 
— scenery, dining, dancing, boating and the 
Swiss wine-country are the draws at the 
shores of the great Lake Geneva (Lac 
Léman) with a view of Swiss and French 
Alps; world-wide renowned for its Béjart 
Ballet Lausanne.</string>
    <string name="about_text_dialects_luzern">Luzern (ger ; eng/fre: Lucerne; ita/roh: 
Lucerna) — main medievial city of the 
Central region with direct water links to all 
of the early Swiss historic sights at the end 
of the many branched lake Lucerne 
(Vierwaldstättersee ends into the river 
Reuss) along of many steep mountains; 
also famous for its tremendous and ethnic 
carnival (Lozärner Fasnacht) around 
February; host of the world-renowned 
Lucerne Festivals, a classical summer music 
festival in the Culture and Congress Centre 
(KKL) designed by Jean Nouvel; starting 
point for many excursions into the Alps.</string>
    <string name="about_text_dialects_lugano">Lugano (ita/eng/ger/fre/roh) — a bustling 
old-town in Italian-spoken Switzerland, at 
the southern end of the Alps with a 
Mediterranean climate at the pretty lake of 
Lugano in the middle of forested 
mountains; much Italianata combined with 
Swiss seriousness.</string>
    <string name="about_text_dialects_stgallen">St. Gallen (ger (also: Sankt Gallen); eng: 
St. Gall; fre: Saint-Gall; ita: San Gallo; roh: 
Son Gagl) — main city of north-eastern 
Switzerland, renowned for its Abbey of 
St. Gall, a UNESCO World Heritage Site and 
its library contains books which date back 
to the 9th century, it also functions as the 
gate to the very exclusive Appenzell region.</string>
    <string name="about_text_dialects_zurich">Zurich (eng/fre; ger: Zürich; ita: Zurigo; 
roh: Turitg) — largest city of Switzerland at 
the end of Lake Zurich (ends into the river 
Limmat), a major centre of international 
banking and national major companies and 
media; great culture &#38; arts possibilities; 
more than 50 museums and around 100 
galleries; great restaurants (more than 
1500) and bars (more than 500); excellent 
cinema selection (~60 show rooms); has a 
thriving nightlife (~80 clubs on weekends); 
host of the largest European party rave 
Street Parade in August with almost 
1 million visitors every year; renowned 
opera, excellent theatre; host of the 
renowned theatre festival Zürcher Theater 
Spektakel during August; every third 
inhabitant is a foreigner.</string>
    <string name="about_mustsee_title">MUST SEE</string>
    <string name="about_text_mustsee_grindewald">Grindelwald — the classic resort at the foot 
of the Eiger</string>
    <string name="about_text_mustsee_spiez">Spiez — a picture postcard town with the 
loveliest bay of Europe</string>
    <string name="about_text_mustsee_rhine">Rhine Falls — the largest falls of Europe, 
close to Schaffhausen</string>
    <string name="about_text_mustsee_zermatt">Zermatt — famous mountain resort at the 
base of the mighty Matterhorn</string>
    <string name="title_activity_explore_luzern">Lucerne</string>
    <string name="symbols_title_swisscross">SWISS CROSS</string>
    <string name="symbols_text_swisscross">The Swiss Cross, as it is often called by the 
native population, is a generalization of the coat of arms of canton Schwyz, one of the 
three founding members of the Swiss confederation back in 1291.
\n
\n
Schwyz apparently played a leading role in the early days, so its name soon was being 
used for the confederacy as a whole. When 
the old Swiss went to battles, the soldiers of each federal state had their own style of 
clothing and carried their own cantonal banner with them. As the confederation 
grew, they needed a common symbol to recognize friend from foe and applied white 
stripes in the form of a cross on their clothes and helmets.
\n \n

During the middle ages, Switzerland was first part of Charlemagne\'s great continental 
European empire (around A.D. 800). His 
sons split the empire in three parts, the eastern part (including Italy, the Alps and 
Germany) was called Holy Roman Empire of German Nation.
\n
\n
When the German emperor once went to
Italy around 1230, soldiers from Schwyz accompanied him. It is reported that he was 
very pleased about the support they gave him and granted them the privilege to add 
a white cross to their red banner.
\n \n 
An old legend says that one of the last
Roman emperors, Constantin, used a banner with a cross symbol when he 
defeated his rival Maxentius in 312. It is very likely that the cross symbol was taken 
over by Charlemagne and his successors as a sign of their leadership over the \"Christian continent\"</string>
    <string name="symbols_title_flag">Who founded Switzerland\’s National flag?</string>
    <string name="symbols_text_flag">If you go right back to the very origins of 
Swiss troops using the white cross on red banners, this was a privilege granted by 
German emperor Friedrich II, so you would suggest that he \"founded\" the Swiss flag.
But if you are asking for the person who convinced a majority of Swiss politicians to 
use a common national flag instead of a 
variety of cantonal banners in 1840, when the white cross on a red square emblem 
was officially introduced as the Swiss army flag, this was Guillaume Henri Dufour, who 
later became general of the federal troops in the short Sonderbundskrieg (civil war) in 
1847 and co-founder of the International 
Committee of the Red Cross in 1864. Of course, it was also Guillaume Henri Dufour 
who proposed the red cross on white ground as the emblem and name for the 
Red Cross.
\n \n

Considering the origins of Switzerland\'s flag 
one should say that the white cross on a red square background symbolizes nothing 
more than just being part of the (once) \"Christian Occident\".
\n \n
The introduction of a tricolor in 1798 and 
the name Helvetic Republic by the Swiss Revolution symbolized that the dominance 
of the old members of the Swiss confederation was broken. The abolition of 
both tricolor and helvetic name and the restauration of cantonal flags inevitably 
marked the return to power of conservative 
anti-centralistic forces in 1815.
\n \n


Discussing the introduction of a common 
national flag in the 1830\'s was part of the process leading to a federal state (instead 
of a loose confederacy). It was certainly more than mere coincidence that the very 
same man, general Guillaume Henri Dufour, who advocated the use of the white cross on red background as Switzerland\'s national 
flag, was the one who, as commander of the federal troops, decided the civil war in 
favour of national unity. (The civil war had been unleashed by conservative 
\"cantonalists\".)
\n \n


On the other hand, using the old cross 
symbol and colors referring to canton Schwyz in the heart of conservative central 
Switzerland instead of the Helvetic tricolor flag referring to the centralist Helvetic 
Republic of 1798 marks a compromise: a political development leading to more centralism than the conservatives wanted 
was being symbolized with a major symbol of the conservatives instead of using a 
liberal symbol. Quite clever - one of the thousands of compromise solutions that 
have guaranteed Switzerland\'s famous and all but evident political stability as a 
federal nation composed of four different 
ethnic/language based regional cultures.
\n \n


To sum it up: For the Swiss, the 
introduction of Switzerland\'s national flag in 1840 and its widespread use 
instead of the cantonal flags symbolizes first and foremost that Switzerland has 
found its national identity and that the 
national identity has become more important than the disparate cantonal 
identities that have dominated Switzerland\'s history from 1291 (Federal Charter) to 1848 (modern Federal 
Constitution).</string>
    <string name="symbols_title_alphorn">ALP HORN</string>
    <string name="symbols_text_alphorn">With the passing of time, the alphorn almost
 totally disappeared as an instrument used by Swiss shepherds. It was only with the 
romanticism of the 19th century and the revival of folklore and tourism that the 
alphorn experienced a renaissance and even became a national symbol.</string>
    <string name="symbols_title_dog">ST. BERNARD DOG</string>
    <string name="symbols_text_dog">The Saint Bernard dog is a special symbol of 
Switzerland. Everyone knows that the large and good-natured Barry saved the lives of 
lost mountaineers. The four-legged hero has always been bred at the Alpine Pass of 
Great Saint Bernhard.</string>
    <string name="symbols_title_chocolate">CHOCOLATE</string>
    <string name="symbols_text_chocolate">During the more than 400 years since 
Columbus became the first European to see cocoa beans, Switzerland has come to the 
forefront of chocolate manufacturing worldwide. Swiss chocolatiers have created 
such delights as truffles, pralines, cakes, and mousses (enough to make a Swiss child 
forget about the bread ) … Swiss chocolate 
is great on its own, or with an espresso, a sweet wine, whisky or a Cognac, and on 
any conceivable occasion.</string>
    <string name="symbols_title_absinth">ABSINTH</string>
    <string name="symbols_text_absinth">The production of Absinthe – also called 
\“Green Fairy\” was prohibited for over 90 years. Since 2005 the mythical liquor, which 
is based on the distillation of various plants and herbs, can again be legally consumed.
This liquor with its tasty bitterness originated in the Val de Travers. Absinthe 
was first distilled in the 18th century in the 
Val de Travers as a medicinal elixir from wormwood, aniseed, fennel and other 
herbs; today it is popular once again, even used to flavour chocolates and pastries. </string>
    <string name="symbols_title_watchmaking">WATCHMAKING</string>
    <string name="symbols_text_watchmaking">For centuries, Switzerland has been 
world-renowned for its watches. This was not always the case: When mechanical 
timekeeping started back in the 14th century, Switzerland lagged far behind the 
times.
\n \n
Watchmaking only began in Switzerland after the Huguenot refugees brought the manufacture of portable timepieces to 
Geneva in the second half of the 16th century. At that time, Geneva, the city of 
Calvin, was a veritable boom town.</string>
    <string name="symbols_title_knife">SWISS ARMY KNIFE</string>
    <string name="symbols_text_knife">The manufacturer from the Swiss Knife 
Valley knows that functionality and usefulness alone are not sufficient to 
appeal to the emotions of the consumer. Only good design which gives an aesthetic 
voice to the intelligent function endows 
products with an unmistakable identity which turns satisfied customers into loyal 
customers.
\n \n
 In 1884, the original knife workshop was 
established by Karl and Victoria Elsener and the first delivery of knives to the Swiss Army 
was made in 1891. When Karl Elsener created the "Original Swiss Army Knife" in 
1897, he could never have imagined that this would become the symbol for quality, 
functionality and Swiss inventive talent all over the world. Nowadays, the "Swiss Army 
Knife" enjoys international protection and, 
more than any other product, stands for the world-famous "Swiss Made" label of quality.</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_text_default">The Canton of Lucerne (German: Luzern) is 
located in the centre of Switzerland. 
The cantonal capital is Lucerne. 
\n \n
In this wonderful city you can take a look at 
the beautiful lake of Lucerne surrounded by 
mythical mountains. Enjoy the sight of 
well-preserved medieval Altstadt (Old 
Town). This city has a reputation for making 
beautiful music. It\’s covered with bridges, 
sunny plazas, candy-coloured houses and 
waterfront promenades.</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_title_pilatus">HIKING ON MOUNT PILATUS</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_text_pilatus">Mount Pilatus assures the best panoramic 
view of Lucerne on a clear day. The visit to 
Mt. Pilatus is a real excitement. 
The cogwheel rail takes off from the base 
of the mountain and travels through the 
most unique railway track. The railway 
goes through the mountains, ice, tunnels 
and lot more eye catchy places and finally 
leads you to the peak. Areal cableways and 
gondolas are also available for the trip. 
Hiking and toboggan sledging are offered 
for the visitors here. Some restaurant 
terrace view of Mt. Pilatus is also amazing.</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_title_rigi">HIKING ON MOUNT RIGI</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_text_rigi">Mount Rigi is named as \“Queen of the 
Mountains\”, and this is obviously for 
reasons. This is not only a high mountain 
but also a place closest to heavenly nature. 
There are a lot of interesting and exciting 
stuffs you can do there. Few of them are 
sledging or skiing in winter and in summer 
time- hiking. Mt. Rigi authority has made 
the place far more exciting by providing 
some services like sunrise ride and dinner 
in cable car, sleigh rides drawn by horse, 
nostalgic steam show and so on. 
Furthermore, events like wrestling 
competition and musical show are organized 
in an occasional basis.</string>
    <string name="explore_history_title">HISTORY</string>
    <string name="explore_culture_title">CULTURE LANDMARKS</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_history_text_history">Lucerne grew up around a Benedictine 
monastery, founded about 750 on the right 
bank of the Reuss by Murbach Abbey in 
Alsace, of which it long remained a \"cell\". It 
is first mentioned in a charter of 840 under 
the name of Luciaria, which is probably 
derived from the patron saint of the 
monastery, St Leodegar. The name Lucerrun 
is first mentioned in 1252. At some point, 
a small village grew up around the 
monastery. The first signs of a municipal 
constitution appear in 1252.
\n \n
With the growing power of the Habsburgs in 
the area the ties that bound Lucerne to 
Murbach weakened. In 1291 the Habsburgs 
finally purchased Lucerne from Murbach. 
The purchase of Lucerne by the Habsburgs 
drove the three forest cantons (Uri, Schwyz 
and Unterwalden) to form an Eternal 
Alliance, an act that is considered to be the 
foundation of Switzerland. In 1332 Lucerne 
became the fourth member of the 
Eidgenossen or Swiss Confederation, and 
the first town to join the rural forest 
cantons.
\n \n
The Battle of Sempach solidified Lucerne\'s
place in the Swiss Confederation
\n \n
Amstaldenhandel, an event in the history of 
the canton of Lucerne, Switzerland
The Battle of Sempach (1386) near Sempach 
(which while allied wouldn\'t become part of 
the canton for 8 more years) drove the 
Habsburgs out of the region and 
strengthened the Confederation. That 
victory led also to the gradual acquisition 
of territory ruled by and from the town.
\n \n
Amstalden, a wealthy innkeeper Schüpfheim 
in the Entlebuch valley of the canton of 
Lucerne, was the leader of a planned 
rebellion of the valley against the city of 
Lucerne. In a plot to limit the power of the 
city, officials from the neighbouring canton 
of Obwalden had promised their support. 
The conspiracy was detected before they 
could stage the planned coup. On 24 
August 1478, Amstalden was arrested, 
tortured and interrogated, and finally 
beheaded in November 1478.
\n \n
The incident furthered the distrust amongst 
rural and urban cantons in the Old Swiss 
Confederacy and was one of the reasons for 
the conclusion of the Stanser Verkommnis 
(Treaty of Stans) in 1481, an important 
coalition treaty of the cantons of the Old 
Swiss Confederacy
\n \n
During the Reformation Lucerne remained 
attached to Roman Catholicism, of which 
ever since it has been the great stronghold 
in Switzerland. The papal nuncio resided 
here from 1601 to 1873. In the 16th 
century, during the early modern age, the 
town government fell into the hands of an 
aristocratic oligarchy, whose power, though 
shaken by the Swiss peasant war of 1653 in 
the Entlebuch, lasted till 1798. Under the 
French-supported Helvetic republic 
(1798–1803) Lucerne was the seat of the 
central government. When the republic 
collapsed, under the Act of Mediation 
(1803) it was one of the six \"Directorial\" 
cantons and during the Restoration 
(from 1815 to 1848) it was one of the three 
ruling cantons.
\n \n
The patrician government was swept away 
by the cantonal constitution of 1831. But in 
1841 the Conservatives regained power. 
They quickly recalled the Jesuits, who had 
been expelled by earlier radical 
governments, to head the cantonal school 
system. The riots that followed brought 
about the Sonderbund War (1847) in which 
the Conservatives were defeated, the 
decisive battle taking place at Gisikon, not 
far from Lucerne.</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_history_title_culture_chapel">CHAPEL BRIDGE</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_history_subtitle_culture_chapel">The town\'s landmark</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_history_text_culture_chapel">Constructed in first half of the 14th century 
as a part of the city\'s fortifications and
named after St. Peter\'s Chapel, which is 
located nearby.
\n \n
The paintings that were added in the 17th 
century illustrate scenes of Swiss and local 
history, including the biographies of the 
city\'s patron saints, St. Leodegar and St. 
Maurice.</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_history_title_culture_tower">WATER TOWER</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_history_subtitle_culture_tower">Archive, treasury and prison</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_history_text_culture_tower">This octagonal tower - over 34 meters high 
(111.5 ft.) - was built around 1300 as part 
of the city wall and used as an archive, 
treasury, prison and torture chamber.
\n \n
It is Lucerne\'s landmark and the most 
frequently photographed monument in 
Switzerland.</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_history_title_culture_lion">LION MONUMENT</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_history_text_culture_lion">Constructed in first half of the 14th century 
as a part of the city\'s fortifications and
named after St. Peter\'s Chapel, which is 
located nearby.
\n \n
The paintings that were added in the 17th 
century illustrate scenes of Swiss and local 
history, including the biographies of the 
city\'s patron saints, St. Leodegar and St. 
Maurice.</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_landmarks_title_lake">LAKE OF LUCERNE</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_landmarks_text_lake">If you\'re not averse to breathtaking 
mountain scenery - perhaps a glance or 
two at a shimmering expanse of water with 
majestic steep peaks of limestone hunched 
over the coastline, forests coming down to 
the shore filled with deer, chamois, foxes, 
and Alpine-native marmots; and fertile 
hillsides, meadows and valleys beyond - 
then this lake won\'t disappoint.</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_landmarks_title_reuss">THE REUSS RIVER</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_landmarks_text_reuss">At the foot of the Gotthard and Furka Pass 
several smaller rivers merge and form the 
Reuss River. At the beginning the river is 
turbulent: In the Middle Ages, the river 
impeded the development of the Gotthard 
Pass in the steep Schöllenen Gorge. Up to 
the point where it flows into the fjordlike 
Lake Uri, the Reuss shares the valley with 
the expressway and the railway line of the 
Gotthard transit route.</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_landmarks_title_pilatus">MOUNT PILATUS</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_landmarks_text_pilatus">No mountain in the long northern arc of the 
Alpine foothills shows such a marked 
upwards thrust as Mount Pilatus on Lake 
Lucerne. Its rock consists of cretaceous 
sediment and Tertiary deposits. 
The calcerous rocks of Mount Pilatus were 
formed in the sea which stretched between 
the Aare and the Gotthard massif. Mussel, 
oyster, ammonite, echinite and sea snail 
fossils today discovered in the Mount Pilatus 
rock provide valuable documentation and 
evidence of when and where the fairly dense 
cliffs and fine slate layers of the mountain 
were created.</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_title_lucerne">RENAISSANCE LUCERNE HOTEL</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_adress_lucerne">www.marriott.de</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_phone_lucerne">+41 41 226 87 87</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_title_alpina">HOTEL ALPINA</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_adress_alpina">www.alpina-luzern.ch</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_textadress_lucerne">Pilatussstrasse 15, Lucerne, Switzerland</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_textadress_alpina">Frankenstrasse 6, Lucerne, Switzerland</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_phone_alpina">+41 41 210 00 77</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_title_hotel">THE HOTEL</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_adress_hotel">the-hotel.ch</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_textadress_hotel">Sempacherstrasse 14, Lucerne, Switzerland</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_phone_hotel">+41 41 226 86 86</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_title_cascada">CASCADA SWISS QUALITY HOTEL</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_adress_cascada">www.cascada.ch</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_textadress_cascada">Bundesplatz 18, Lucerne, Switzerland</string>
    <string name="explore_luzern_stay_phone_cascada">+41 41 226 80 88</string>

</resources>